'I was right about mikhail.
'He's got something
going on with matti.'
the pa?
You need to find out if your friend
cyclops has been playing you.
inadvertently or not.
'Could you have been set up?'
you're gonna have to
trust my judgment on this.
Unless you think I'd lie
to you? Of course I don't.
I'll drop the petition
if you agree to respect
my personal life.
I'm sure you'll handle whatever
blows you might have to take.
just like I did.
Have you had chance to
think about this loan. yet?
Because I'm running out of time.
Your comrades
won't bail you out?
The foreign secretary's decision
to meet with the
Russian foreign minister
is part of a wider pattern
of questionable judgements.
She deserves everything
she's gonna get.
Agreed.
Looks like the Swiss
lawyer owns an offshore.
Like a middle man for Ryan?
If we really wanna find out. I
need to go fishing in Geneva.
If we can place Igor and any
cabinet ministers or sis staff
in the same place at the same
time. then we might have something.
I won't have long.
I'll need dates. When
was his special unit set up?
I'm working on it.
'Ryan Walker took
payments from Igor borodin.
'Sauverre brokered the entire
deal through his offshore.'
game over. Ryan.
Kate had concerns about
your personal security.
I'm the foreign
fucking secretary.
I don't need any
covert surveillance!
Do not meddle with
the Democratic process.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Kate?
Rose called me.
Where is he?
What did he find out?
Did they take anything?
Have you got his phone. laptop?
That's gone. You're sure?
Yeah.
Leave it.
The counter terror
team are on their way.
I'll deal with them. You
don't have the authority.
I'm not giving them
classified material.
I said leave it!
You got here quick.
I was at the office.
I'll take it from here.
Wait outside. Stall the met.
I'm sorry.
You told him? I have
to follow protocol.
I need to lock these files down.
When was the last
time you spoke to rav?
An hour ago.
He went to Geneva.
He met Ryan's middleman.
We've got copies of wire
transfers Moscow made to Ryan.
How did he get
blown? I don't know.
Our mole in sis
tracked his phone.
or the lawyer suspected
rav and told Moscow
and they realised that
rav was getting too close.
so they had to shut him down?
But to kill him in London.
Have you told the chief?
Yes.
I always thought
he was unshockable.
He'll see you first thing.
That'll be the met.
Let's get this over with.
My love... I'm
so sorry. darling.
If I'd have gotten
there sooner...
Well. then it could have
been you. couldn't it?
You can't carry on like this.
You can't.
Why the hell hasn't
this finished him?
You'll win because you're
a woman of infinite class.
Crawler. What do you want?
This is Imogen Conrad.
Whispers: It's the mail.
Yes. Caroline. What
can I do for you?
'..Material emerging...'...
'I was wondering if you
have any comment?'
I have no comment.
What's happened?
Shit.
Everything ok?
It's over. What's over?
Everything's over.
Imogen's career. our
campaign. it's done.
No. I don't wanna watch it.
Please. Well. don't look. then.
Shit!
Who is he? No idea.
I'm not watching it again.
ok? Did you know about it?
Yeah. I mean. we knew they
had something. but not this. no.
So. it's real. then? It
doesn't really matter.
The real question is.
why the hell has that ended
up in Ryan Walker's hands?
Yeah.
I'm gonna make a move before
any more vultures descend.
Sorry.
This isn't your mess.
I don't know what to say. Harry.
You could say it didn't happen.
It's another bit of fake news.
That'd be a start.
"No comment."
Imogen!
I'm very sorry about
your colleague.
It's unthinkable.
Thank you. sir.
You're sure it was Moscow? It...
It seems like a huge provocation.
We'll wait for the official
verdict from counter terror.
but there's no
real doubt our end.
And. yes. a British
agent on home turf
is an alarming step change.
Rav got proof that Ryan Walker
was paid by Moscow centre.
Paid for what?
A piece of land he
wanted to develop.
his old union car park.
A Swiss lawyer
brokered the deal.
most likely a contact
from lev amatov. Right.
I see you went against my
express request not to investigate.
Rav confirmed the cash originated
from a Moscow centre bank account.
We advise you suspend
Ryan. prime minister.
and then he'd have to withdraw
from the leadership race.
It's not that simple.
I understand how
serious this is. but...
if I'm seen to be interfering
in the Democratic process
without concrete proof...
I've just showed you the proof.
Yes. of dishonesty and
greed. but not espionage.
Well. surely. you
can postpone the vote
until we've
investigated further?
It also looks like
Moscow's responsible
for the home secretary's sex tape.
which we think Ryan knew about.
We all know how keen the Russians
are to help out pliable politicians.
In my view. Ryan Walker
is undeniably compromised
by this evidence.
But it isn't evidence.
I was a lawyer before
I entered politics.
You've given me
"balance of probability".
and that is not the same as
"beyond reasonable doubt".
The country's already in chaos.
Unproven rumours
of Russian collusion
will only escalate
things further.
With respect. surely that's
a risk you'll have to take.
I'm sorry.
But I'll do more damage in the
long-run if I call off the election.
The answer's no. Thank you.
He thinks Moscow centre
paid a British minister
several million quid in
exchange for fuck-all?
Party before country.
We should have known that
would be his last job in office.
What do we have left on
the table? Mikhail borodin.
I've got an agent on the ground in
Moscow with an "in" to Igor's unit.
but I need mikhail to play ball.
In exchange for an
"out" from the kremlin?
Will you authorise an approach?
I'm already tracking him in Finland.
You've ignored your orders
so far. as Anthony pointed out.
You might as well try
and finish what you started.
Report direct to me.
Does that mean
you're not telling zak?
Not telling zak what?
Hello?
'Mrs Henderson.
This is Ryan Walker.'
Kate.
Thanks for coming.
Can I get you anything?
No. I'm good. thanks.
Is this where you do
your unofficial business?
I used to come here
as a junior minister.
All-day breakfast for under a
fiver and no Whitehall spies around.
What can I do for
you. foreign secretary?
Well. I wanted to offer my
condolences about ravindra.
Rav.
Thank you. but a phone
call would have been fine.
No. it happened on my
watch as foreign secretary.
While I understand that
we suspect Moscow...
Do we know why
they targeted him?
Perhaps your friend Dmitri
krimsov could shed some light.
I take the threat of Russian
interference in this country
very seriously.
We'll need to work together to
make sure this doesn't happen again.
What do you want. mr Walker?
I want to shake things up.
Kate... In the cabinet and in sis.
Now. Anthony is unfortunately
going. sir Alan's headed for retirement.
You seem pretty
close to zak Hussein.
Zak.
Zak's an arse-kisser. and a
surname like Hussein is a hard sell.
There's no point
pretending otherwise.
Well. you were responsible
for his promotion.
Don't get me wrong. we
need desk jockeys like zak.
but... you take no prisoners.
We have that in common. So
why did you get me suspended?
Let's just call that
an overreaction. ok?
And I think it's time we gave a
bright young talent the top job.
Here's your full
English and your toast.
In return for what?
Look. let's not play games. Ok?
This is hard politics.
Let's help each other.
I've gotta go. Don't
let your eggs get cold.
Hi. Rose.
I've run the sex tape
through diagnostics.
It's definitely been modified.
If it's a deepfake. why
wouldn't Imogen just say so?
Then she'd be off the
hook and back in the race.
Well. perhaps it was altered to
protect the man. whoever he is.
I'll go there now and
see if I can talk to her.
There's something else.
So. I checked the
internal phone logs.
Zak and Julie talk a
lot out of office hours.
Right.
Neighbourhood watch.
I'm not here to tell you off.
That makes you the exception.
Stuart tried to talk
me out of running.
I should have
listened to him. Really?
I thought Stuart wanted you in
downing street as much as I do.
Politically. yeah.
but he did warn me
about the personal cost.
I have to ask...
is the video real or not?
You're not the first mp to be
honey-trapped by a Russian spy
if that's what happened?
We know the tape was tampered
with. What are you fishing for?
Who's the man. Imogen?
Nobody.
Some local guy I met on
that bloody trip to Montenegro.
Are you sure he wasn't Russian?
What was his name?
Honestly. I... don't remember.
It was in a bar. I was drunk.
I've buried the whole thing.
Harry and I... Were
having a difficult time.
I screwed up.
Can we just leave
it at that. please?
How well do you
know zak Hussein?
We cross paths
every now and then.
Did you get to know
him better in Montenegro?
Am I under investigation?
We know you were
there at the same time.
The hotel conference?
I didn't see him there.
I was too busy working lev.
Harry's charity was
about to go under.
Lev had just dangled
a big donation.
You went to a cocktail party
with a man named kyril markov?
God knows.
I met a bunch of men who wanted
to have their picture taken with me.
Lev said they were
hotel investors.
Well. he forgot to mention
that kyril is one of Moscow's
most senior intelligence officers.
Kate. is this why you're here?
To Bury me. after this
tape has just killed me off?
There's a lot of public support
out there for you already.
Yes. well... No other mp
has had a million tweets
about the size of their
tits. have they? I'm fucked.
And if I call the critics out.
I'm an angry black woman.
The story's already written.
By who? Ryan Walker?
The man you're about to
let become prime minister?
Do you know something I don't?
Are you investigating him?
If I said yes... Would
you stay in the race?
I knew it.
Look. I don't know what really
happened in portonovi - yet.
But I do know that you're
not working for Moscow.
If you drop out now...
you're handing Ryan
the keys to number 10.
Sorry to interrupt.
Finished with the
picture-hanging?
Yeah. the Matisse
went into lev's office.
Do you wanna have
a look? Another time.
Amanda. the car's
waiting for you outside.
Lev. got a minute? Yeah.
All right. bye.
Is everything all right?
No. it's not.
You've heard the mylar
project's about to collapse?
I did. Unfortunate. Unfortunate?
It's a fucking disaster.
If the company's dissolved.
I'll be named and shamed.
I understand.
What sort of figure
are we looking at?
I need a million to
protect my investment.
Then I'm good for
it when the flats sell.
That's a considerable
amount of money.
Trust me. I wouldn't
ask unless I had to.
You can rely on us.
The funds through the
same channel as before. Ok.
Thank you.
We've always felt any
investment in Ryan Walker
was bound to be a sound one.
We backed the right man.
Leave it with me.
Yeah.
Sorry. I don't understand.
How can you just.
"overturn" a suspension?
It's complicated.
Well. where are you going?
What are you gonna tell the kids?
Well. you know I can't
tell you where I'm going.
I've told them it's a final
work trip to tie up loose ends.
I'll be back by tomorrow.
Jesus Christ. Katie.
Your agent has been killed.
Your deputy has been killed.
Our daughter has just
almost been kidnapped.
Haven't you had enough?
Yes. I have had enough.
But I have no choice.
There's always a choice.
We can't keep going on like
this. Surely you understand that?
Look. Jim's here.
He'll look after you.
When I get back.
we'll take a break.
Do you promise? I promise.
Please be careful.
Please. I will.
I always am.
I thought you were
gonna wear the dark grey?
It's not a funeral.
It will be for Imogen if
she doesn't show up.
Here. It's fine.
Do you still want me to come?
Aren't you too busy
with other affairs?
Please don't jump
to conclusions.
Please don't treat
me like an idiot.
You've got your career. Ryan.
I need something...
To hurt me with?
No. something to
make me feel alive.
You chose lev?
The art expert?
The humanitarian with
bottomless pockets?
Did he tell you he's just
bailed me out for a million quid
when daddy didn't come through?
He can afford it. Well.
I can't. Nor can you.
Where do you think the loan
for the union land came from?
A British building society?
Well. you said... I thought
your dad... Nah. I lied.
If either loan gets traced
back. my career's over.
So is yours.
So. there you go.
Lev's fucked us both.
I hope you enjoyed
it more than I have.
Hi. it's Kate. 'Hi. Come
up to the sixth floor.'
ok. Thank you.
Hi.
Thank you.
It must be his regular
spot. The waiter knew him.
How secure is the cafe?
There are no street
cams and no minder.
Are you sure you're up to this?
Yeah.
Yeah. I just...
Rav.
I know.
Julie. does anyone
else know you're here?
Apart from me and Rose?
No. of course not.
Ok. Let's go.
Hey.
'Fucking hell. I've
been worried sick.'
what was there to say?
'Are you dropping out of the
race? If you are. I'd understand.'
look. I made a mistake.
and I'm being punished for it.
I don't see why the
public should be too.
If Ryan wins. they will be.
I'll see you at hq. all right?
Let's go. Before I
change my mind.
Hi. can I take
some sugar? Clear.
Is this a safe neighbourhood.
mikhail? I'm visiting from London.
It's a nice spot.
You must enjoy being
away from Moscow.
And your father.
How's matti?
Did you know that Lena knew
about your affair with him?
She kept your secret for you.
She was as scared of
your father as you are.
If you're here to
blackmail me...
You know that's not our style.
I'm here to offer you a way out.
In England? You think
they won't find me there?
I can hide you anywhere -
Europe. Canada. Australia.
I won't leave my son.
I understand.
You have no idea. I
have kids too. mikhail.
I know what it's like
to lead a double life.
And it's better for sandro
if you stay together.
We'll make it work.
When? I can fast-track it.
but I'll need something
to set things in motion.
Such as?
The name of the asset your
father has in the British cabinet.
Is that all?
And the identity of the agent
inside sis who's helping you.
My father keeps those
secrets very close to his chest.
Well. I'll need a
decent down-payment
on your British passport.
And I'll need to be in London
before I empty my pockets for you.
My guess is that both the
cabinet asset and the sis agent
are run out of the same unit?
Somewhere on
your father's floor?
The unit is his pride and joy.
And he brought in
kyril to run logistics?
When was the unit set up?
You looking for the keys to
the safe here. mrs Henderson?
Come on. mikhail.
I need a way in.
December '24.
You'll have the rest
when I'm in London.
My agent will contact you here.
'Igor set up the unit
in December 2024.
'Look for any foreign trips he
took that month or just before it.'
Minutochku.
Pozhaluysta.
Prokhodite.
But I don't know. If
she's not gonna show up.
maybe she's withdrawn
her leadership bid.
That would be too
easy. Ryan. even for you.
How long till the announcement?
Er. any minute now. Thank you.
Is there something you
wanna tell me. Julie?
It's just sex.
How long have you two been
together? We're not together.
It's not a big deal.
He's your boss.
And mine. You
should have told me.
I knew you'd judge me for it.
Yeah. for your taste in men. maybe.
Does everyone know?
He said Rose was
asking about Dubrovnik.
So. you were there with him?
Well. he was there for
some intelligence pow-wow.
I just flew out for the weekend.
Did he mention any
business in portonovi?
He said he'd gone to pitch for
an agent. but the guy didn't show.
Do you think he actually
could've been there
to meet kyril markov?
Could he be working for him?
Zak?
Somebody in the system is
feeding Moscow intelligence.
Lena's dead. rav. so that
leaves us. Rose. c and zak.
No. It's not him.
I mean. zak is a lot of things.
but he would never betray
his country or the service.
Wh-who was he there to
turn? Did he mention anyone?
No. but he was in a
foul mood all weekend.
Fuck. Maybe Moscow set him up.
Dangled the prize of kyril
markov just to get him out there.
What. and confuse us? Yeah.
To get us to ask questions
that we can't answer.
Like why Imogen. kyril and zak
were all in the same
place at the same time.
So. zak got played?
Yeah. he'd definitely
try and hush that one up.
Sorry. just a sec.
Yeah? Igor borodin was in Prague
from the 12th to the
14th of December. 2024.
Are you there?
Yeah.
I hope it's enough to
catch your informer.
And the minister.
So do I.
I'm gonna take a long route
out and go dark for a while.
Thank you.
You're not on your own.
You know where to find me.
Take care of
yourself. 'You too.'
Everything all right?
Er. yeah. I've got...
I've got some dates...
Check the office mainframe.
all government travel records.
including those that
cover members of our staff.
Prague. 12th to the
14th of December. 2024.
Imogen Conrad received
46.9% of the vote.
Thank you. Brilliant.
Ryan Walker received 53.1%.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you.
Every effort that was made.
I'm so appreciative. Every effort!
Thank you so much.
Every effort. thank you so much.
- Hi.
- 'We lost.
'Ryan's in.' I saw.
'It does makes you wonder
why we bother. doesn't it?'
everything ok your
end? Not really.
'Why? What's happened?'
my work thing didn't play out.
I'm in Finland.
You ok. though? 'I'll
explain when I see you.'
why don't you come
out for a few days?
We can go back to that hotel.
What. the one by the lake?
Yeah. near virolahti.
What about the kids?
'I've spoken to Rose.
'She said she'd stay over.'
we owe ourselves some
time. don't you think?
'Great.'
I'll book a flight. 'Today?'
yeah. Tonight.
'Good.'
bye.
Don't.
What's happening?
Why are we here? I'm
offering you an escape route.
Russian border's down
there. You can walk to it.
I've asked the Finns
to open it for you.
And then what?
Go and find Igor borodin.
Like you did on our
anniversary. in Prague.
when he recruited you.
I know you had an affair
with Imogen in Montenegro.
They erased you from the original
sex tape in return for information.
And all this time. I was
looking for a mole in my office.
It wasn't an affair.
It wasn't. It was
a... It was one time.
And it was... it was a
really stupid mistake.
but that was it. we were drunk.
Why didn't you just tell me that
you were being blackmailed?
Cos I knew you'd leave me.
And this is better?
Katie. they said to me all
wanted was... like. cabinet gossip
and... And then they
wanted more information -
about me. about my movements.
They had me by the
fucking balls by then.
People died!
I know they did!
Stuart. people died! I know.
You put our
whole family at risk.
Look. they... they promised
me they would never hurt you.
They would never hurt the
children. that's what they said. ok?
That's what they said.
Kate. I am asking
you to forgive me.
Please. It's too late.
It's not too late. It's
not. It isn't. It isn't.
I love you. and I know a
part of you still loves me.
That's why I'm letting you go.
I don't want Fiona and Gus to
see you going on trial for treason.
Look. it can't end like
this. It can't. It can't.
Bye. Stuart. Katie... please.
Come on.
How are the children coping?
Confused. Angry.
You did the right thing.
A trial was
unthinkable for all of us.
I'd like to secure
visiting rights
once all of this has cooled off.
In a neutral country. Of course.
Although. who's
to say they will cool
with Ryan Walker
in downing street?
Yeah. You might as well
have copied a set of keys
and sent them to Moscow centre.
And now he's got the power
to stop all lines of inquiry.
including ours.
Well... I'm sure
you'll find a way in.
You always do.
Does zak know about
your plans to leave?
Not yet.
Now's your chance
to tell him. Kate.
You've lost the
battle. but not the war.
You all right?
It was a lovely service.
Rav would have
hated the attention.
Look...
i wanted to clear the
air before I step back.
I should have trusted you.
I'm sorry.
"Step back"?
No-one's career survives
sleeping with the enemy.
I know what you've
had to sacrifice.
That counts for
something in my book.
I got a lot of things
wrong. We both did.
But not the important ones.
Anyway. we've got plans for you.
We need you back. Kate...
Before our new prime minister
starts changing the
wallpaper in downing street.
So. you do think he's
working for Moscow?
The one thing we do know... Is
that they've created chaos here.
and that may be
exactly what Igor wanted.
You know their game
better than anyone...
and our job is to work
together to beat them.
Let me think about it.
I can't find my homework.
Is it done or undone?
Done. actually.
Well. there's
fresh juice. no bits.
Found this in the bathroom.
I'll be late tonight. mum.
I've got football. Ok.
Do you want a croissant? You
don't have to do this. you know.
Do what? Pretend
that everything's perfect.
You're only human.
I'm working on it.
Mum. Yeah?
Still frozen in the
middle. Really?
Yeah. Sorry.
It's a bit hard. It's
really bad. Don't eat that.
Before I walk in
through this famous door.
I just want to take a moment...
To make you all a promise.
I am here to listen to you.
It's no accident that there
were so many attempts
to stop me from being here -
civil servants.
intelligence agents.
and the politicians they
can bend to their will
via misinformation and smears.
All the tools of the deep state.
Well. let me tell you something.
the days of the arrogant
ruling elite... are over.
Because despite them. the
party's chosen me to govern.
And my duty is and
always will be to you...
The people.
Thank you.
Care to comment?
Prime minister!
Are you planning major
changes. prime minister?
Congratulations. Thank you.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Welcome to downing
street. prime minister.
Thank you. Congratulations.
Thanks. zak. You already
know Kate Henderson.
We've seconded her
to the cabinet office.
Right. What. to
keep an eye on me?
To keep you safe from
any hostile influences.
I'll certainly do my
best. prime minister.
Subtitles by
accessibility@itv.Com
Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app